Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Area, 166005
  - Hebrew Union, 166336 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony at Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_03; 166338; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Construction of Hebrew Studies Center, 1978; wsa_3_6_04; 166337; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - "House of Genius" (61 Washington Square South), 1948; 166333 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - South Side of Washington Square South Looking East from Thompson Street, 1948; wsa_3_7_01; 166335; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Genius Row, undated; wsa_3_7_02; 166334 (Box 177, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Jefferson Market 6th Avenue and 9th street), 166325 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_01; 166332; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_02; 166331; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_03; 166330; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_04; 166329; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Jefferson Market, Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_8_05; 166328; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - People Gathering Signatures Against the Closing of the Jefferson Market Library, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_06; 166327; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 6)
    - Jefferson Market Police Court (engraving), 1878; wsa_3_8_07; 166326; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - Map (circa 1820-30), 1820-1839; 166323 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Map of Greenwich Village (engraving), 1822; wsa_3_9_01; 166324; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - MacDougal Street, 166286 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - North Side of MacDougal Alley Looking East From MacDougal Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_01; 166322; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Washington Square South and MacDougal Street, 1962; wsa_3_10_02; 166321; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - MacDougal Street and Washington Square South, undated; wsa_3_10_03; 166320; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - West Side of Washington Square West Looking North from West 4th Street, 1947; wsa_3_10_04; 166319; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 4)
    - MacDougal Street, Between Minetta Lane and West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_05; 166318; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 5)
    - MacDougal Street South of West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_06; 166317; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking East from Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_10_07; 166316; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 7)
    - East Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from West 8th Street, 1947; wsa_3_10_08; 166315; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 8)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking West 8th from MacDougal Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_09; 166314; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 9)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking North from Minetta Lane, undated; wsa_3_10_10; 166313; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 10)
    - MacDougal and West 3rd Street Looking West on West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_11; 166312; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 11)
    - Calypso Club, MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_3_10_12; 166311; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 12)
    - South Side of West 4th Street Looking East from Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_10_13; 166310 (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 13)
    - South Side of West 8th Street Looking West from MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_3_10_14; 166309; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 14)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from West 8th Street, wsa_3_10_15; 166308; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 15)
    - East Side of Sixth Avenue looking south from West 4th Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_16; 166307; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 16)
    - East side of Sixth Avenue Looking North from West 3rd Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_17; 166306; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 17)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking north from West 3rd Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_18; 166305; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 18)
    - East side of Sixth Avenue looking south from West 8th Street, circa 1947; wsa_3_10_19; 166304; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 19)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from Minetta Place, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_20; 166303; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 20)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking north from West 3rd Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_21; 166302; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 21)
    - Buildings 114-120 Along MacDougal Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_22; 166301; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 22)
    - Intersection of MacDougal Street and Washington Square South/West 4th Street, 1962; wsa_3_10_23; 166300; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 23)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking south from West 4th Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_24; 166299; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 24)
    - South side of West 4th Street Looking West from MacDougal, ca 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_25; 166298; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 25)
    - South side of MacDougal Alley, circa 1947; wsa_3_10_26; 166297; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 26)
    - MacDougal Street, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_27; 166296; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 26)
    - 118 MacDougal Street, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_28; 166295; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 28)
    - MacDougal Street - Square Tavern, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_29; 166294; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 29)
    - MacDougal Street - No. 138, Bat Restaurant, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_30; 166293; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 30)
    - MacDougal Street - No.138, Ground Floor Hallway, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_31; 166292; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 31)
    - Le Figaro Cafe, circa 1950s; wsa_3_10_32; 166291; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 32)
    - MacDougal Street - Washington Square Art Show, 1955; wsa_3_10_33; 166290; Abbott, Albert; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 32)
    - MacDougal Street - View of Calypso Club, circa 1950s; wsa_3_10_34; 166289; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 34)
    - MacDougal Street - Rear of No. 144, Interior Court, circa 1950s; wsa_3_10_35; 166288; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 35)
    - MacDougal Street - Caffe Reggio, circa 1980s-1990s; wsa_3_10_36; 166287; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 36)
  - Mercer Street, 166277 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1956; wsa_3_11_01; 166285; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - Mercer Street Looking East, 1965; wsa_3_11_02; 166284; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Looking South on Mercer Street, circa 1950s-1960s; wsa_3_11_03; 166283; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 4 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Corner of Mercer Street and Waverly Place, circa 1950s-1960s; wsa_3_11_04; 166282; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - Mercer Street, 1964; wsa_3_11_05; 166281; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1964; wsa_3_11_06; 166280; Luigi Pellettieri (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 6)
    - Mercer Street - Hot Dog Vendor, 1981; wsa_3_11_07; 166279; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1964; wsa_3_11_08; 166278; Luigi Pellettieri (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 8)
  - Parsons School of Design/New School, 166274 (Box 178)
    - Parsons School of Design, circa 1960s-1970s; wsa_3_12_01; 166276; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 2 ½ inches (Box 177, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - Parsons School of Design, circa 1960s-1970s; wsa_3_12_02; 166275; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 177, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - New Sailors' Snug Harbor Properties, 1947-1955; 166265 (Box 178)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, 1947; wsa_3_13_01; 166273; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Washington Mews No. 12 - South side, looking east, 1948; wsa_3_13_02; 166272; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Washington Mews No. 12, 1948; wsa_3_13_03; 166271; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Folder 3)
    - Washington Mews, No. 12, circa 1947; wsa_3_13_04; 166270; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 4)
    - Washington Mews No. 12 - south side, looking east, circa 1947; wsa_3_13_05; 166269; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 5)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, circa 1946; wsa_3_13_06; 166268; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 6)
    - 262 Sailors Snug Harbor, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_13_07; 166267; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 7)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, Looking East, 1955; wsa_3_13_08; 166266; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 8)
  - Provincetown Playhouse, 1936; 166263 (Box 178)
    - Provincetown Playhouse, 133 MacDougal Street, 1936; wsa_3_14_01; 166264; Abbott, Berenice, 1898-1991; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178)
  - 6th Avenue, 1940s, 1940-1949; 166251 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Looking North at East Side of Sixth Avenue, From Washington Place Towards Waverly Place., Circa 1940-1949; wsa_3_15_01; 166262; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 1)
    - 6th Avenue "El" Turning West Into West 3rd and West Broadway, circa 1940-1949; wsa_3_15_02; 166261; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 3/4 x 6 5/8 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 2)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, from West 8th Street, 1945; wsa_3_15_03; 166260; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 3)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, From Washington Place, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_04; 166259; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 4)
    - Looking East from 6th Avenue at the North Side of Waverly Place, 1945; wsa_3_15_05; 166258; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 5)
    - West Side of 6th Avenue Between 3rd and 4th Streets, 1945; wsa_3_15_06; 166257; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 6)
    - Looking North at East Side of 6th Avenue, from West 4th Street, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_07; 166256; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 7)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street, looking South from Intersection of Washington Square South and Washington Square West, 1945; wsa_3_15_08; 166255; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 8)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, from Washington Place, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_09; 166254; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 9)
    - Looking North at East Side of 6th Avenue, towards 8th Street, 1945; wsa_3_15_10; 166253; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 10)
    - 6th Avenue, 1860; 166252 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - 6th Avenue, 6th and 14th, 217047 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - Slum Clearance Project (Between West 3rd and Houston), 1950-1959; 166245 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - 6th Avenue El turning west onto West 3rd Street, wsa_3_17_01; 166250; Roberto, Joseph J.; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 3/4 x 6 5/8 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 1)
    - Site of Loeb Student Center, demolition of old building, Washington Square South, November 12, 1957; wsa_3_17_02; 166249; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 2)
    - Demolition, Washington Square South, June 19, 1957; wsa_3_17_03; 166248; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 3)
    - Washington Square Project, Southeast Slum Area, West Houston between Wooster and West Broadway (north side)., 1955; wsa_3_17_04; 166247; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Washington Square Project, Southeast Slum Area, North side of West 3rd Street between Wooster and W. Broadway., 1955; wsa_3_17_05; 166246; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 5)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue's Cemetery (West 11th Street), 1970; 166241 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_01; 166244; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 1)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_02; 166243; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 2)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_03; 166242; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 3)
  - Studio Building (51 West 10th), 1858; 166239 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Studio Building, 51 West 10th Street, 1858; wsa_3_19_01; 166240; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Fires, NYU and area, 166382 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Fire Alarm at Rubin Residence Hall (exterior), 1981; wsa_3_1_01; 166406; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Firemen, undated; wsa_3_1_02; 166405; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Westside Pier, undated; wsa_3_1_03; 166404; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Firefighter at Work in Silhouette, undated; wsa_3_1_04; 166403; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Fire at Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_3_1_05; 166402; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_06; 166401; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_07; 166400; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_08; 166399; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Aftermath of Fire in Main Building, 1983; wsa_3_1_09; 166398; Chait, Marc W.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_10; 166397; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_11; 166396; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books, undated; wsa_3_1_12; 166395; black-and-white print (photograph), 2 x 3 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_13; 166394; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Silhouette of Fireman, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_14; 166393; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_15; 166392; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Fireman, undated; wsa_3_1_16; 166391; Shiotani, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Fire on Sullivan Street, 1983; wsa_3_1_17; 166390; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Fire, Sixth Avenue, 1981; wsa_3_1_18; 166389; Comer, Philippe; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_19; 166388; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Firefighters, undated; wsa_3_1_20; 166387; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_21; 166386; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_22; 166385; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Fire, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_3_1_23; 166384 (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books (exterior), undated; wsa_3_1_24; 166383; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 24)
  - Grace Church, 166380 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Grace Church (engraving), undated; wsa_3_2_01; 166381; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Subway Stations, 166233 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Subway Station (West 4th Street), 1980; wsa_4_1_01; 166238; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - TSOA Students at West 4th Street Subways, 1988; wsa_4_1_02; 166237; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 2)
      Student activities.; Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.)
    - 7th Avenue Subway Station, wsa_4_1_03; 166236; Occhiogrosso, Paul; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Subway Entrance 6th Avenue and West 3rd Street, circa 1950-1959; wsa_4_1_04; 166235; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - 8th Street Subway Station, 1973; wsa_4_1_05; 166234; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Sullivan Street, 166227 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Sullivan Street and Washington Square South, Aerial View, wsa_4_2_01; 166232; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 ½x 4 ½ inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Googie's Bar, 1981; wsa_4_2_02; 166231; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Googie's Bar, 1981; wsa_4_2_03; 166230; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Sullivan Street and Washington Square South, wsa_4_2_04; 166229; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Newsstand, wsa_4_2_05; 166228; Gurian, Mal; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 1/4 x 9 3/4 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Thompson Street, 166217 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Washington Square South and Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_01; 166226; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 1/2 x 4 3/4 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Looking South at East Side of Thompson Street, from Washington Square South, wsa_4_3_02; 166225; Mantel, Muriel; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Pinto's on Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_03; 166224; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Looking North along Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_04; 166223; Cole, Roberto, 1915-; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 3/4 x 7 1/2 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Arch Cafe on Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_05; 166222; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Ernie's, 1959; wsa_4_3_06; 166221; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Oasis at Washington Square South and Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_07; 166220; Beals, Jessie Tarbox; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Thompson Street and West Broadway, wsa_4_3_08; 166219; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - Looking North at the East Side of Thompson Street, circa 1948; wsa_4_3_09; 166218; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - Trinity Trade School (35 Washington Square West), 1942; 166214 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Trinity Trade School, no. 35 Washington Square West, undated; wsa_4_4_01; 166216; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Trinity School, Wall Street Divisions, 1942; wsa_4_4_02; 166215; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Twain, Mark - Residence of (14 West 10th Street), 1970; 166212 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Mark Twain House, 14 West 10th Street, 1970; wsa_4_5_01; 166213; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Unidentified photos of Washington Square Area, 166160 (Box 179, Folder 8)